Negative
A World of Sorrow
Tonight, all my faith has died
The earth drank it up to the very last drop
Tonight, I was alone in the world
Deep in my heart, the desire was fading
To live alone in a world of sorrow
A cold desert, endless nights
Even when dawn breaks, the days are grey
With a life like this...
Tonight, I turned my eyes toward the sky
Searching for a star
beneath which I could stand
But they had all fallen down to earth
And gave me the strength to admit to myself
That I live alone in a world of sorrow
A cold desert, endless nights
Even when dawn breaks, the days are grey
With a life like this, even death tempts me
I live alone in a world of sorrow
A cold desert, endless nights
Even when dawn breaks, the days are grey
With a life like this, even death tempts me
Tonight, the angels folded their wings
Turned their heads the other way
And gave me the strength to admit to myself
That I live alone in a world of sorrow
A cold desert, endless nights
Even when dawn breaks, the days are grey
With a life like this, even death tempts me
I live alone in a world of sorrow
A cold desert, endless nights
Even when dawn breaks, the days are grey
With a life like this, even death tempts me
I live alone in a world of sorrow
Endless nights
And death tempts me
Death tempts me...
Tonight, I turned my eyes toward the sky
Searching for a star
beneath which I could stand
But they had all fallen down to earth
And gave me the strength to admit to myself